[
  {
    "id": "T5A01",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Electrical current is measured in which of the following units?",
    "answers": [
      "Volts",
      "Watts",
      "Ohms",
      "Amperes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A02",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Electrical power is measured in which of the following units?",
    "answers": [
      "Volts",
      "Watts",
      "Watt-hours",
      "Amperes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A03",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is the name for the flow of electrons in an electric circuit?",
    "answers": [
      "Voltage",
      "Resistance",
      "Capacitance",
      "Current"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A04",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What are the units of electrical resistance?",
    "answers": [
      "Siemens",
      "Mhos",
      "Ohms",
      "Coulombs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A05",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is the electrical term for the force that causes electron flow?",
    "answers": [
      "Voltage",
      "Ampere-hours",
      "Capacitance",
      "Inductance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A06",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is the unit of frequency?",
    "answers": [
      "Hertz",
      "Henry",
      "Farad",
      "Tesla"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A07",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Why are metals generally good conductors of electricity?",
    "answers": [
      "They have relatively high density",
      "They have many free electrons",
      "They have many free protons",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A08",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following is a good electrical insulator?",
    "answers": [
      "Copper",
      "Glass",
      "Aluminum",
      "Mercury"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A09",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following describes alternating current?",
    "answers": [
      "Current that alternates between a positive direction and zero",
      "Current that alternates between a negative direction and zero",
      "Current that alternates between positive and negative directions",
      "All these answers are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A10",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which term describes the rate at which electrical energy is used?",
    "answers": [
      "Resistance",
      "Current",
      "Power",
      "Voltage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A11",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What type of current flow is opposed by resistance?",
    "answers": [
      "Direct current",
      "Alternating current",
      "RF current",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T5A12",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What describes the number of times per second that an alternating current makes a complete cycle?",
    "answers": [
      "Pulse rate",
      "Speed",
      "Wavelength",
      "Frequency"
    ]
  }
]